As Prophet T.B. Joshua prays for individuals in the name of Jesus Christ,
the evidence of God's mighty presence is clear.
The people move and fall against their will under the mighty anointing of the Holy Ghost.
Everything that was in the dark is exposed,
including the demons operating in their lives.
Manifestation Of Evil Spirits
I am her ancestors!
I am the ancestral spirit of the family.
Manifestation Of Evil Spirits
He is the one that disturbs me!
I want to fight him; I am after him.
Him and his Jesus...
I am going to kill her!
I entered her since she was a baby; she is mine!
I want to fight you!
I control her and I will control her all her life!
I control her through her thoughts.
She will never succeed!
They tried to deliver her but we will never let her go. She belongs to me; she belongs to us.
She is part of us!
I made her do immoral things; I torment her!
Day and night, I torment her when she is praying.
Prophet T.B. Joshua delivers the woman in the name of Jesus Christ,
casting out the evil spirit behind all her afflictions.
She is free.
Thank You, Jesus!
TESTIMONY CONTINUES
Ms Carina
From French Guiana Living In France
She said her name is Carina. She is living in Paris, France. She is originally from French Guiana.
Ms Carina
Deliverance Testimony
As you saw it on the video, I'm here to give a testimony for the glory of God,
for what He has done in my life.
Ms Carina
Deliverance Testimony
She said that everything started in her life when she was around five to six years old.
In the family she is coming from, they used to perform some rituals and they used to do it for herself.
They would prepare some concoction and put it in some water and liquid.
They would then be bathing her with that concoction and liquid,
be washing her body but she never knew what the purpose of these rituals was.
She said that when she was eight to nine years old, she moved from French Guiana to Paris, France.
When she was 15 years old, she decided to go back to French Guiana
and that is how the spirit started manifesting within her.
She started developing that spirit of lust towards men.
She said that any man she would be looking at, as soon as they had eye contact,
the man would be following her to be sleeping with her.
Ms Carina
Deliverance Testimony
She said that at that time when she was 15 years old and she went back to French Guiana,
she started sleeping with so many men in one year
that she can't even count how many men she was sleeping with in that one year
because she was having this spirit of lust that was controlling her.
She said that when she went back to Paris, France, one year later,
it even became worse. She started going to nightclubs, dancing, smoking and drinking
and sleeping with different men. With those she had an eye contact with, she would be sleeping with them.
She started living this life of immorality.
There is a tradition in her country, French Guiana, where you join a group of carnival
and you would be wearing a mask and be dancing.
She joined this group when she went back to Paris, France.
Ms Carina
Deliverance Testimony
She said that this is the kind of group that she joined.
We can see those people wearing masks, like a masquerade group.
She said that in joining them, she would be like possessed and be dancing with men.
There would be eye contact as they could only see each other's eyes.
At the end of the day, the only thing after that would just be sleeping with men.
Joining this kind of group was very funny.
It is now that she realised that she was really possessed.
She said that during the week, she could be very sick and down.
But when it was time to wear this kind of mask and attire and she put the mask on,
the sickness would just vanish and she would feel very well and strong
to perform these kind of rituals and at the end of the day, she would be sleeping with many men.
Ms Carina
Deliverance Testimony
So she said that she became like a princess in the nightclub.
At a time when she went to nightclubs, they would know her so well.
She didn't pay for anything anymore. She would be drinking and smoking for free.
They would be giving her things. All the men would be coming around her.
She can't count how many men she has been sleeping with.
She said that the kind of men she used to meet, she knows that they are occult men.
Many at times they were like demons because she always met them at night.
Even when she was about to sleep with them, it would always be in the dark.
They didn't want the light to be on. It would always be in the dark.
They would be asking her to do so many different things.
Some would be asking her to be urinating on them, masturbating them
or using some objects to be sleeping with them.
That demon made her to do a lot of different things that naturally, a normal human being would not do.
She realised that it was really a life of immorality that she was living.
Ms Carina
Deliverance Testimony
That spirit even made her to be sleeping with men that maybe, she would be attracted to
and even with men that she would not even think of looking at -
men she would not even be attracted to and she would be sleeping with them,
to tell you that that spirit would choose whoever she would be sleeping with.
Whoever would be coming her way, she would be sleeping with them.
She said that this really affected her, to the point that she even met a man one day
that introduced her to sleeping with another woman.
That was how she started having an attraction towards women.
But that day, that man introduced her to sleeping with another woman.
That is how the spirit has really destroyed her life.
Ms Carina
Deliverance Testimony
That spirit even caused her to pierce her neck.
She was having a piercing at her neck, her nose and the lower part of her lips.
If God had not rescued her, she would be having a lot of piercings all over her body.
Ms Carina
Deliverance Testimony
She said that that spirit even made her to have different kinds of hairstyles -
red style, shaved at the side, different kinds of styles that any normal human being wouldn't have
like she would sometimes look like a chicken.
This evil spirit would make her to do different kinds of hairstyles.
Ms Carina
Deliverance Testimony
She said that because of this problem, she was seeing that she was really falling down.
She was used to those rituals that they used to do to her when she was small
so she was consulting witchdoctors, different seers to get a solution to her problem
and they would be giving her different concoctions to drink, things to use on her body,
and different things to be doing. At the end of the day, she would even become worse and worse
in the immorality she was living.
Can you explain to us now - how did you get to know about The SCOAN
and now come to receive your deliverance?
Ms Carina
Deliverance Testimony
She said that when she saw that this problem had brought different kinds of problems into her life -
she was into debt, she was not suceeding professionally,
everything was not working around her, she was really in the dark -
she started watching Emmanuel TV after she had discovered Emmanuel TV on the internet.
She started praying with the man of God, Prophet T.B. Joshua
and she realised she needed to come to receive her deliverance.
So when you came and the man of God, Prophet T.B. Joshua, prayed for you, what happened?
Ms Carina
Deliverance Testimony
So she said that when the man of God was coming towards her to pray for her,
before he even came in front of her, she was feeling a sensation, vibration in her body.
When the man of God touched her, she really felt...
She saw on the video how she reacted and she said that she really realised
how satan had been using her, had been living in her body and had been destroying her life.
She realised that really those rituals they used to do for her when she was small
were transmitted to her from generation to generation as the spirit said he was an ancestral spirit.
She said that after the man of God, Prophet T.B. Joshua, touched her
and the spirit manifested, she is now feeling so free and fine.
Let's clap our hands for our Lord Jesus Christ for what God has done in the life of this lady!
So now that you are feeling free and so fine, can you tell us -
do you still have the desire to sleep with men as you look around,
do you still have that eye contact? All those bad dreams you used to have, are they still there?
Ms Carina
Deliverance Testimony
She said that she is totally free. She doesn't have any desire to sleep with any man.
She doesn't have any desire to drink or smoke.
No more bad dreams. She is completely free for the glory of God.
Let's clap our hands for our Lord Jesus Christ!
She has been removed from the kingdom of darkness into the kingdom of light
and we give thanks to God for her life today.
For what the Lord has done in your life, what is the advice you have
for young ladies, young people like you that may be facing the same kind of situation
and don't know how to go about it?
Ms Carina
Deliverance Testimony
She said she has three advices for people.
First of all, she would like to advice young ladies, especially coming from the islands.
When you are going to a traditional dance or things like a carnival,
don't see it as something very light as there is a spirit behind it -
a spirit that will possess you to go and do those hidden vices.
Ms Carina
Deliverance Testimony
She said that she also wants to tell young ladies - that is her second advice -
that sometimes, don't let the mirror deceive you.
Don't believe that maybe because you are beautiful and well made -
without our Lord Jesus Christ, this beauty is nothing.
Ms Carina
Deliverance Testimony
Her third advice is also for young people:
All these social media - please get free from these social media.
Many a times there are spirits behind it that will possess you.
You will find yourself doing what you don't want to do.
So please, be careful of social media. So these are the three advices she has.
We pray with her that God Almighty will give her the grace to maintain that deliverance she received
in making God's Word the standard for her life, in the mighty name of Jesus Christ.
Ms Carina
Deliverance Testimony
Emmanuel! So she said that she wants to thank God for the life of Prophet T.B. Joshua,
for the love he showed to her, for the hospitality, for allowing her to stay one more week
and being in the presence of God and being able to give this testimony today.
She wants to tell everybody: Please, the Lord is not far from you.
He is just behind the door; you just need to open that door for Him to step in
and He will do the same thing He has done for me in your life, in the mighty name of Jesus Christ.
Let's clap our hands for our Lord Jesus Christ!
TT: Mel Flowers 16/06/2018
RV: Pavel Tatyana Zheleznyakov 30/07/2018